membersuite.com 2013-12-01

# MemberSuite - Privacy Policy

This is a website of MemberSuite, Inc. 

47 Perimiter Center E   
Suite 630  
Atlanta, GA 30346  
(678) 606-0310  
E-mail: info@membersuite.com 

MemberSuite takes privacy on the Internet very seriously. We are the leading provider of enterprise-class, on-demand software for member-based organizations and as such we are committed to the establishment and maintenance of policies and procedures that protect the privacy of personal information that may be collected from customers, prospective customers, partners and others who may visit our website. 

MemberSuite is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not share, sell or rent this information to any third parties, other than what is disclosed in this privacy statement. 

This privacy policy is to inform you of how MemberSuite gathers and uses your personal and other information when you visit our web site. MemberSuite reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by notifying visitors to this web site of the existence of a new privacy policy. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, you may contact us via e-mail at security@membersuite.com. To help us respond in the most timely and appropriate way, please be as specific as possible in your request or inquiry. 

##  Personal Information

We do not collect personal information about you unless you specifically and knowingly provide such information to us. Any information collected is used only by MemberSuite for the purposes stated at the time of collection or as otherwise set out in this privacy statement. MemberSuite collects and uses your information only for the following purposes: 

  * To respond to your requests for further information about our MemberSuite™ on-demand software as a service (On-Demand) offerings, our professional services, and our company.
  * To register for our online demonstration of MemberSuite™.
  * To provide you with subscriptions to MemberSuite newsletters or publications.
  * To provide MemberSuite’ Partners with reliable and quality support.
  * To support operational processes within MemberSuite, such as credit card processing. 
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements.

Following your request for information about MemberSuite's products, we may request your permission to use your personal information for other informative purposes, for example, to send you an email newsletter or for marketing purposes. You will always be provided the opportunity to opt out of further contact by MemberSuite. 

We endeavor to only to collect the personal information necessary in these circumstances. Personal information collected may include your name, address, phone number, fax number, organization, and e-mail address. All personal information collected from the public MemberSuite website is stored in our secure marketing database. Only authorized MemberSuite employees have access to this information. 

Some areas of the MemberSuite website may require use of a username and password for access. This username and password allows you to access certain areas such as online support, the product knowledgebase, product purchases, and other restricted areas of the site. When it is necessary to contact you in connection with a particular online activity, this username and password is cross-referenced against the personal information you have provided to MemberSuite. 

##  Collection of Information

For each visitor to our public web site, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor’s domain name, but not their e-mail address (where possible). We collect e-mail addresses from web site visitors that choose to communicate with us by e-mail, information volunteered by the visitor. MemberSuite may use this information to contact prospective customers for marketing purposes and is not shared with any 3rd party organization for commercial purposes. If you would prefer not to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail with ‘Remove’ as the subject line to info@membersuite.com. 

If you supply us with a postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings with new product information, upcoming events, or company news. If you would prefer not to receive mailings from us, please call the number above and we will remove your name from our mailing list. 

If you supply us with your telephone number online, you may receive telephone contact from MemberSuite with new product information, upcoming events, or company news. If you would prefer not to receive telephone calls from us, please send us an e-mail with ‘Remove’ as the subject line to info@membersuite.com, include your name and phone number, and we will remove your name from our call list. 

To be removed simultaneously from e-mail, phone, and mail lists, please send us an e-mail with ‘remove from all lists’ in the subject line to info@membersuite.com. 

##  With Whom Your Information Is Shared 

The personal information you provide to us through our site may be disclosed to MemberSuite’ authorized reseller partners. We do not sell, trade or share any of your personal information with any other third-party organizations, with the exception of approved credit card processing services. We will release personal information when we believe such release is appropriate in order to comply with the law; for example, if we receive a subpoena, search warrant, or court order. 

##  Cookies

MemberSuite may use a technology called ‘cookies’ to record or track information related to visitors to our public website. Cookies are simple text files that web browsers place on computer hard drives when sites are visited. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell MemberSuite your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information, unless you choose to provide this information when asking for further information from us. For example, requesting product information. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

These cookies are specific to the website session and are not used to record personal information or to associate personal information with the use of the MemberSuite™ service. Users may disable their web browser’s ability to accept cookies without affecting their ability to successfully navigate the MemberSuite public website. 

In order to improve access to content based on visitors' browsers and operating system types, and to make our content available to as many visitors as possible, MemberSuite may collect certain technical information from your computer’s web browser or Internet device when you visit www.membersuite.com. This information includes the amount of time spent on the site by a visitor with a unique Internet identifier, the pages visited and returned to, the operating system, and Web browser used, the referring Web site and any keywords used to find our site on a search website. These server logs do not contain any personal information and can only be accessed by employees of MemberSuite. Server log files are used solely to track visits to our Web site and improve the experience, content and layout of our site. MemberSuite makes no attempt to link this traffic information to the individuals visiting our Web site. 

##  Third-Party Sites 

The MemberSuite website may contain links to other websites. MemberSuite is not responsible for the privacy policies of, or the content of these websites. Website visitors and customers need to read the privacy statements of other websites to understand their privacy policies. 

##  Security

MemberSuite employs technology and security measures in our physical facilities to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Data under our control. When our Site is accessed using Mozilla Foxfire, or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.5 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that Data is safe, secure, and available only to you. MemberSuite also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and hosts the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. The server is protected by an enterprise firewall that is immediately updated when new patches and fixes are released. 

##  Changes to Privacy Policy 

Periodically, MemberSuite may use customer data for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. We will update this policy from time to time. We will always include a ‘last revised’ date as part of our privacy policy. You may check this page periodically to stay informed on MemberSuite’ policy. 

##  Additional Information 

By providing you with this privacy policy, MemberSuite is pledging its continued commitment to protecting the information we collect. We regularly review our information-handling practices to ensure that we are abiding by this policy. If you have questions regarding this statement or the practices of this site, or if you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may e-mail such questions to security@membersuite.com or by regular mail addressed to the Security Administrator at the address included above. 

Last revised 05/10/2010 

##  Hosting Privacy Policy 

For current customers of the MemberSuite™ software service, we are committed to protecting your privacy. One of the ways in which we demonstrate this commitment is through the care we take to protect the privacy of information which we collect when we host your data on our servers. MemberSuite’ hosting services are provided by a recognized leader in providing secure managed hosting that delivers enterprise-class web infrastructure to businesses of all sizes – including Fortune 100 companies. Our provider operates the MemberSuite servers within their secure, state-of-the-art data center. MemberSuite selected our hosting provider based on their ability to provide fast and redundant access to the Internet, world class facilities, and commitment to high availability for MemberSuite’ applications. MemberSuite has entered into service agreements with our provider, with the objective, among others, of protecting the privacy of the people who use our software. 

###  Collected Information:

Users' names and email addresses ("Customer Information") are collected and maintained in the MemberSuite™ application for purposes of managing the login authentication process, and to allow the application to send notifications to the end user. An example of an application notification would be an email notice informing the user that a scheduled task has been completed. 

MemberSuite will not give any Customer Information to a third party, unless we are required to do so in order to comply with the law, or to provide secure credit card processing. 

###  Cookies:

The MemberSuite application utilizes session specific cookies so that only authenticated users can navigate the application. We also support non-session cookies for allowing the user to automatically remember their login credentials to gain access to the application. 

###  Security: 

All hosted environments meet the following physical security requirements…main access monitored with additional access for emergency purposes only; surveillance cameras in facility; access validation with biometric identity check; access only to persons on MemberSuite' approved access list which is managed at the executive level within MemberSuite. 

All hosted environments also meet the following electronic security conditions - login validation; creation of accounts only as verified by MemberSuite; secure SSL (encrypted) connections to access servers; servers running behind secure firewall. 

One of the options we offer is Secure Socket Layer (SSL). If you implement our SSL option, we will not transmit Customer Information for the particular user interface that has the SSL over the public internet "in the clear", i.e., without it first being encrypted.

MemberSuite imposes strict internal controls over those of its employees with access to Customer Information. Such access is granted only on a need to know basis. 

Finally, MemberSuite™ provides unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Data. 

###  Changes to Personal Information: 

Our software is configured to enable you to give your end users the means to access their own personal information for the purposes of deleting it, and/or correcting it. 

##  Changes to Hosting Privacy Policy: 

MemberSuite will update this policy from time to time. A "last revised" date will always be included on the bottom of the statement. To keep up-to-date with MemberSuite' policy, please check this page periodically. 

##  Additional Information 

By providing you with this Privacy Policy, MemberSuite is pledging its continued commitment to protect the information we collect. We regularly review our information-handling practices to ensure that we are abiding by this policy. If you have any questions about this statement, or our practices as they affect the privacy of hosted data, you can contact us on security@membersuite.com 

Last revised 01/14/2007 

For more information about the terms of use of this website, contact info@membersuite.com. 

##  Security Statement

MemberSuite provides state-of-the-art data security and privacy to our clients, ensuring that your data is safe around the clock. MemberSuite devotes significant resources to continuously develop our world-class infrastructure. We know that security is paramount to our clients — and we've made it our highest priority. 

When you subscribe to MemberSuite, you will enjoy unsurpassed protection and peace-of-mind.

###  Security Measures 

* Continuous deployment of proven, up-to-date security technologies and best practices.
* Ongoing evaluation of emerging security developments and threats. 
* Commitment to a secure, scalable, hosted system. 
* Security redundancy throughout the MemberSuite architecture. 

###  World-Class Security

We deliver a security infrastructure comprised of current, proven, cutting-edge technologies. MemberSuite delivers the most comprehensive security available — firewalls and encryption devices sourced from leading Internet security vendors, configured by expert professionals, and rigorously tested before going into production.

**Physical Security**  
Production equipment is located in a secure facility which provides 24-hour physical security through biometric and visual identification, proximity tracking, and video monitoring. Redundant electrical generators, redundant data center chillers and other back-up equipment designed to keep servers up and running are continuously monitored.

**Perimeter Defense**  
Perimeters of production and corporate networks are protected by firewalls developed by leading security vendors.

**Data Encryption (provided upon request)**  
MemberSuite offers 128-bit SSL for secure HTTP connections between client computers and our servers.

**User Authentication**  
Users access MemberSuite’ client websites only with a valid username and password combination, which is optionally encrypted via SSL while in transmission. 

**Application Security**  
Our robust application security model prevents one MemberSuite customer from accessing another's data. This security model is reapplied with every request and enforced for the entire duration of a user session.

**Operating System Security**  
MemberSuite enforces tight operating system-level security by using a minimal number of entry points to all production servers. All systems are hardened and protected with strong passwords, and maintained at each vendor’s recommended patch level. 

**Database Security**  
Whenever possible, database access is controlled at the operating system and enforced at the database connection. Direct access to production databases is restricted to the production and redundant environments.

**Server Management Security**  
All data entered into the MemberSuite application by a customer is owned by that customer.

MemberSuite employees do not have direct access to the MemberSuite production equipment, except where necessary for system management, maintenance, monitoring, and back-ups. 

Note: Use of the MemberSuite™ services are subject to the terms of use in the customer license agreement. MemberSuite may change its security infrastructure and/or this security data sheet from time to time.
